<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News &#8211; Fubo Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://fubo.online.mills.edu/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://fubo.online.mills.edu</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:29:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Litton confident of winning home and abroad sans big names</title>
		<link>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/litton-confident-of-winning-home-and-abroad-sans-big-names/</link>
					<comments>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/litton-confident-of-winning-home-and-abroad-sans-big-names/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://fubo.online.mills.edu/?p=23</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bangladesh Test captain Litton Kumer Das said his young team is now confident of winning home and abroad even without the big names like Shakib al Hasan and Tamim Iqbal. Bangladesh clinched an empathic 546-run win against Afghanistan in their one-off Test match in the fourth morning of the match on Saturday and Litton believes ... <a title="Litton confident of winning home and abroad sans big names" class="read-more" href="https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/litton-confident-of-winning-home-and-abroad-sans-big-names/" aria-label="More on Litton confident of winning home and abroad sans big names">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Bangladesh Test captain Litton Kumer Das said his young team is now confident of winning home and abroad even without the big names like Shakib al Hasan and Tamim Iqbal.</p>
<p>Bangladesh clinched an empathic 546-run win against Afghanistan in their one-off Test match in the fourth morning of the match on Saturday and Litton believes his team is capable of winning Tests.</p>
<p>Litton was captaining the side as their regular captain Shakib al Hasan missed the Test and the Tigers also missed the service of experienced opener Tamim Iqbal. But Litton quickly reminded the side clinched a historic Test away victory against New Zealand last year without those two big names.</p>
<p>“Without Shakib bhai and Tamim bhai we won in New Zealand with a young team. When we won a Test abroad our confidence grew. Everybody started keenly waiting for the next opportunity of playing a Test match. We will not get our three-four senior players after two to three years. If we cannot handle that from now on it will be tough if the change suddenly occurs.</p>
<p>“It would be better had they [Shakib and Tamim] played here, but it does not mean we are unable to come back from there. Our batting order and pipeline is gradually improving. All the newcomers have abilities.”</p>
<p>Litton started his journey as a captain in the most emphatic style and not only the big margin of victory but also the way his teammates performed in all three disciplines made him extremely satisfied.</p>
<p>Litton, who also did the wicketkeeping, was extremely aggressive as it was seen at times five to six players were stationed at slip cordon. Bowlers bouncing to terrorise the opponent batters and some of the balls carrying through to the keeper at a shoulder height thrilled the spectators.</p>
<p>‘’ I enjoyed the captaincy very much. The bowlers helped me a lot… from behind the wicket I saw the bowlers carrying the ball, going through to slips. I had great fun keeping it. Whenever I am captain, I feel good that there is always a chance of picking up wickets,” said a jovial Litton who normally is known as reticent.</p>
<p>“Whenever you have good batters and bowlers the job of captaincy becomes easy. The way Najmul and Mahmudul attacked as a captain I thought it built the base of the match. I thought we were going to be in a strong position although we were supposed to post a big score in the first innings. Due to some silly mistakes we failed to do,’’ Litton praised his young batters.</p>
<div id="0666e1cd-55eb-488b-bf36-52d1afcaf2ec">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>But the most striking thing was the bowling of Bangladesh pacers who not only picked up 14 out of 19 wickets but utilised the green-top by bowling their heart-outs amid extreme tough conditions of high heat and humidity. Litton was in all praise for his pace unit which he believes is gradually improving.</p>
<p>Traditionally spin bowling is the forte for Bangladesh sides especially at the low and slow home soils. But the recent Test saw lively pitch that was conducive for pacers as well as help for spinners who can bowl well.</p>
<p>Litton appreciates these kinds of wickets so all his bowlers get chances to showcase their skills and he looked forward to the future after getting success against Afghanistan.</p>
<p>The traditional wisdom suggests Test cricket is the test of attrition where players must show patience, resilience and caution. Batters have been advised for decades to protect their wickets and check hitting instincts.  But with the emergence of shorter format batters around the world have become more adventurous with the mantra of more and more attack.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="4378bc5a-e8b8-4809-85d7-a4bb80917282">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>England team has taken ultra-aggressive style of “Bazball’ to throw away all the cautions to score runs in ultra rapid manner. Bangladesh also batted aggressively in both the innings, scoring around 4.5 per overs in the first innings to accumulate 382 and around five and a half for 426 in the second innings.</p>
<p>Litton, who himself is regarded as the most aesthetic stroke maker of the country, thought the aggressive approach is effective and has become a norm in modern day cricket.</p>
<p>“If the batter thinks the ball is there to hit, it is better to hit. Why should you leave when you get the chance of hitting it? Flow of runs also put opponents under pressure. Test matches used to be termed as five day matches in old days but most of the matches are not lengthening up to fifth day these. Over the last few years everybody is trying to score quickly and declare if they have good bowlers.”</p>
<p>With those words Litton seemed to give the message that Bangladesh is not only looking for more success but their approach to Test cricket is getting more aggressive and modern.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/litton-confident-of-winning-home-and-abroad-sans-big-names/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vinicius and Brazil spot on with black strip anti-racism protest</title>
		<link>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/vinicius-and-brazil-spot-on-with-black-strip-anti-racism-protest/</link>
					<comments>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/vinicius-and-brazil-spot-on-with-black-strip-anti-racism-protest/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:27:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://fubo.online.mills.edu/?p=20</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[On a night in which Brazil wore an all-black strip to protest racism in football, Vinicius Junior was on the score sheet and in the spotlight in a 4-1 international friendly win over Guinea. The 22-year-old Real Madrid forward has been subjected to frequent racist abuse this season and Brazil decided the freindly was a ... <a title="Vinicius and Brazil spot on with black strip anti-racism protest" class="read-more" href="https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/vinicius-and-brazil-spot-on-with-black-strip-anti-racism-protest/" aria-label="More on Vinicius and Brazil spot on with black strip anti-racism protest">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>On a night in which Brazil wore an all-black strip to protest racism in football, Vinicius Junior was on the score sheet and in the spotlight in a 4-1 international friendly win over Guinea.</p>
<p>The 22-year-old Real Madrid forward has been subjected to frequent racist abuse this season and Brazil decided the freindly was a good opportunity to strike back as the match was staged in Espanyol’s stadium near Barcelona.</p>
<p>In a powerful move Brazil abandoned their iconic yellow and green shirts and were instead kitted out in an all-black strip in a stand against racism for the first half of the game.</p>
<p>The Brazilian Football Confederation was behind the gesture accompanied by the slogan of “Com racismo nao tem jogo” (With racism, there is no game).</p>
<p>Vinicius himself, wearing the number 10 shirt, got on the score sheet with an 88th minute spot-kick, by this time kitted out in Brazil’s usual colours.</p>
<p>Newcastle forward Joelinton was well placed to tap-in the opener on the goal-line on 27 minutes while Rodrygo curled home the second two minutes later.</p>
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>Stuttgart striker Serhou Guirassy pulled a goal back with a close range header on 35 minutes but Eder Militao restored the two-goal lead shortly after the restart rising high to meet a cross at the far post.</p>
<div id="d16bc9da-abcb-4b65-ba6d-5e5e233f1eb6">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS KMFZK qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>Manchester United midfielder Casemiro escaped with a yellow card for a late tackle on Francois Kamano that was at odds with the party atmosphere in the stadium.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="9d1ea1f6-8414-44d3-8a18-fddc3df23c1a">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>Late in the game Brazil substitute Malcom was brought down in the box and Vinicius was urged to take the penalty, which he hit hard and low enough to beat ‘keeper Ibrahim Kone who had dived the right way.</p>
<p>Earlier in the week the Spanish and Brazilian football federations presented their plan for a friendly match at the Santiago Bernabeu in March 2024 to combat racism following global outrage at the abuse of Vinicius Junior.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/vinicius-and-brazil-spot-on-with-black-strip-anti-racism-protest/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>England bowl out Australia for 386 after Khawaja falls for 141</title>
		<link>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/england-bowl-out-australia-for-386-after-khawaja-falls-for-141/</link>
					<comments>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/england-bowl-out-australia-for-386-after-khawaja-falls-for-141/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[user]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2023 13:26:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://fubo.online.mills.edu/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Australian Usman Khawaja’s mammoth innings came to an end when he was bowled for 141 by Ollie Robinson before lunch on day three of the first Ashes Test on Sunday, as the tourists just failed to surpass England’s first-innings total of 393. Australia, who resumed on 311 for five on a warm, overcast morning at ... <a title="England bowl out Australia for 386 after Khawaja falls for 141" class="read-more" href="https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/england-bowl-out-australia-for-386-after-khawaja-falls-for-141/" aria-label="More on England bowl out Australia for 386 after Khawaja falls for 141">Read more</a>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Australian Usman Khawaja’s mammoth innings came to an end when he was bowled for 141 by Ollie Robinson before lunch on day three of the first Ashes Test on Sunday, as the tourists just failed to surpass England’s first-innings total of 393.</p>
<p>Australia, who resumed on 311 for five on a warm, overcast morning at Edgbaston, lost both settled batters Khawaja and Alex Carey before three more wickets fell in quick succession as the visitors ended on 386 – seven runs short of England&#8217;s first innings score.</p>
<p>Khawaja played with great composure for most of his knock, showcasing his experience as he picked off the singles and kept the ship steady.</p>
<p>However, as England captain Ben Stokes piled on the pressure with an aggressive field placement comprised of six catchers, Khawaja took the bait, charging down the wicket before Robinson’s inch-perfect yorker uprooted his off-stump.</p>
<p>Earlier, James Anderson was denied Carey’s wicket in the day’s first over due to a Jonny Bairstow drop, but an angling delivery from the veteran bowler snared the Australian for 66 two overs later, ending his 118-run stand with Khawaja.</p>
<div id="fec66576-14cd-4385-98bf-b776dbe24591">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS KMFZK qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>Australia captain Pat Cummins contributed 38 runs, hitting Moeen Ali for two sixes in an over before the spinner briefly left the field for treatment on an injury to his spinning finger.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
<div id="ed48730b-4a64-4ede-99ff-c480966a711e">
<div class="storyCard eyOoS qwBlA">
<div class="   
                  story-element"></p>
<div class="story-element story-element-text">
<div>
<p>Earlier on Sunday, the ICC said England all-rounder Moeen Ali had been fined 25 per cent of his match fee for breaching the code of conduct on day two of the test after applying drying spray to his finger without permission from the on-field umpires.</p>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
</div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://fubo.online.mills.edu/2023/06/18/england-bowl-out-australia-for-386-after-khawaja-falls-for-141/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
